What do you feel is the president's role? There's been so much conversation in the past few years
just about how I think a lot of people are reimagining what the actual role of the presidency
is as people get a lot more aware of local politics, right, of our senators and, you know,
representatives and how they operate. What do you feel the president's role at this point is?
You know, Franklin Roosevelt said that the primary job of the presidency is not administrative. He
said the primary job of the president is moral leadership. The way I look at the US government,
Washington is filled with a lot of political car mechanics and some of them are good political
car mechanics, but that's not the problem. The problem is we're on the wrong road. We don't
need another technician. Specifically, you hire technicians. They work for you and your administration
and so forth. We need a visionary. We need somebody to remind people what our mission statement, what
what does all men are created equal mean?